Inventory of the Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills records 1872-1994 MS004
Archives & Records Management, Library and Information Center, Georgia Institute of Technology
- Operative reports, 1913-1922.; SERIES 3; 2.8 Linear feet; (7 document cases)
  - Atlanta mill, 1913-1922.; SERIES 3, Subseries 1; 2.0 Linear feet; (5 document cases)
    - A14-08-COR: Correspondence: Day's Detective Agency, August 1914 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - A14-09-OP18: Operative #18, September-October 1914 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - A14-10-OP36: Operative #36 (folder 1 of 2), October 1914 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - A14-10-OP36: Operative #36 (folder 2 of 2), October 1914 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - A14-10-OP457: Operative #457 (folder 1 of 5), October 1914- January 1915 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - "Report of Operative #457", October 14, 1914; MS004-166
      - "Report of Operative #457", November 6, 1914; MS004-167
      - "Report of Operative #457", November 13, 1914; MS004-168
      - "Woman Organizer Comes From Great Southern Strike", ca. 1914; MS004-169
    - A14-10-OP457: Operative #457 (folder 2 of 5), October 1914- January 1915 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - "Report of Operative #457", November 20, 1914; MS004-170
      - "Report of Operative #457", December 6, 1914; MS004-171
    - A14-10-OP457: Operative #457 (folder 3 of 5), October 1914- January 1915 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - "Report of Operative #457", December 15, 1914; MS004-172
      - "Report of Operative #457", December 20, 1914; MS004-173
    - A14-10-OP457: Operative #457 (folder 4 of 5), October 1914- January 1915 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - A14-10-OP457: Operative #457 (folder 5 of 5), October 1914- January 1915 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - "Report of Operative #457", January 14, 1915; MS004-174
      - "Report of Operative #457", January 31, 1915; MS004-175
    - A14-12-OP16: Operative #16 (folder 1 of 16), December 1914- August 1916 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - A14-12-OP16: Operative #16 (folder 2 of 16), December 1914- August 1916 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Report of Operative #16, January 4, 1915; MS004-176
    - A14-12-OP16: Operative #16 (folder 3 of 16), December 1914- August 1916 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Report of Operative #16, January 20, 1915; MS004-177
    - A14-12-OP16: Operative #16 (folder 4 of 16), December 1914- August 1916 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Report of Operative #16, February 10, 1915; MS004-178
    - A14-12-OP16: Operative #16 (folder 5 of 16), December 1914- August 1916 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - A14-12-OP16: Operative #16 (folder 6 of 16), December 1914- August 1916 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - Report of Operative #16, March 2, 1915; MS004-179
    - A14-12-OP16: Operative #16 (folder 7 of 16), December 1914- August 1916 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Report of Operative #16, March 15, 1915; MS004-180
      - "Mass Meeting under the Auspices of the Atlanta Federation of Trades", March 21, 1915; MS004-181
      - Report of Operative #16, March 16, 1915; MS004-182
      - Report of Operative #16, March 17, 1915; MS004-265
    - A14-12-OP16: Operative #16 (folder 8 of 16), December 1914- August 1916 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - "Mass Meeting: Labor Forward Movement", April 18, 1915; MS004-183
    - A14-12-OP16: Operative #16 (folder 9 of 16), December 1914- August 1916 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - A14-12-OP16: Operative #16 (folder 10 of 16), December 1914- August 1916 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Report of Operative #16, May 6, 1915; MS004-184
      - Memo concerning Operative #16 and Sara Conboy, May 4, 1915; MS004-185
      - Report of Operative #16, May 10, 1915; MS004-186
      - Report of Operative #16, May 10, 1915; MS004-187
    - A14-12-OP16: Operative #16 (folder 11 of 16), December 1914- August 1916 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - A14-12-OP16: Operative #16 (folder 12 of 16), December 1914- August 1916 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Report of Operative #16, June 25, 1914; MS004-188
      - Memo concerning Operative #16 and burning Governor Slaton in effigy, June 25, 1915; MS004-189
    - A14-12-OP16: Operative #16 (folder 13 of 16), December 1914- August 1916 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Report of Operative #16, August 13, 1915; MS004-190
      - Report of Operative #16, August 15, 1915; MS004-191
    - A14-12-OP16: Operative #16 (folder 14 of 16), December 1914- August 1916 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - A14-12-OP16: Operative #16 (folder 15 of 16), December 1914- August 1916 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Letter from H. N. Brown, Railway Audit and Inspection Company, to Oscar Elsas, January 28, 1916; MS004-192
      - Report of Operative #16, March 26, 1916; MS004-193
    - A14-12-OP16: Operative #16 (folder 16 of 16), December 1914- August 1916 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - A15-04-OP10: Operative #10, April 1915 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - A16-08-OP429: Operative #429 (folder 1 of 2), August-October 1916 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - "Operative #429, Special Work, Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills", August 22, 1916; MS004-195
      - "Operative #429, Special Work, Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills", September 9, 1916; MS004-196
      - "Operative #429, Special Work, Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills", September 10, 1916; MS004-197
      - "Operative #429, Special Work, Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills", September 11, 1916; MS004-198
      - "Operative #429, Special Work, Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills", September 12, 1916; MS004-199
    - A16-08-OP429: Operative #429 (folder 2 of 2), August-October 1916 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Report of Operative #429, September 26, 1916; MS004-200
      - Report of Operative #429, October 7, 1916; MS004-201
    - A18-04-OP185: Operative #185 (folder 1 of 3), April-May 1918 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Report of Operative #185, April 23, 1918; MS004-202
    - A18-04-OP185: Operative #185 (folder 2 of 3), April-May 1918 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - A18-04-OP185: Operative #185 (folder 3 of 3), April-May 1918 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Report of Operative #185, May 15, 1918; MS004-203
      - Report of Operative #185, May 26, 1918; MS004-204
    - A18-06-OP2,100: Operatives #2, 100 (folder 1 of 2), June 1918 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Letter from John W. Weccard, American Detective Service Company, to G. A. Johnstone, Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills, June 11, 1918; MS004-205
    - A18-06-OP2,100: Operatives #2, 100 (folder 2 of 2), June 1918 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - "Evening Report Fulton Bag Company [from Operative #100, Ole R. Olsen]", June 9, 1918; MS004-206
    - A18-06-OP760,230: Operatives #760, 230 (folder 1 of 3), June-July 1918 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - A18-06-OP760,230: Operatives #760, 230 (folder 2 of 3), June-July 1918 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - A18-06-OP760,230: Operatives #760, 230 (folder 3 of 3), June-July 1918 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - A18-06-OP207: Operative #207, August-September 1918 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - A18-08-OP7418: Operative #741B (folder 1 of 4), August-September 1918 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Letter from Operative #741B, Sherman Service, to F. H. Neely, Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills, September 6, 1918; MS004-207
    - A18-08-OP7418: Operative #741B (folder 2 of 4), August-September 1918 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Report of Operative #52, August 24, 1918; MS004-208
      - Report of Operative #52, August 28, 1918; MS004-209
    - A18-08-OP7418: Operative #741B (folder 3 of 4), August-September 1918 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - A18-08-OP7418: Operative #741B (folder 4 of 4), August-September 1918 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Report of Operative #52, September 20, 1918; MS004-210
    - A18-08-OP1082: Operative #1082, August 1918 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - A18-12-OP713: Operative #713 (folder 1 of 2), December 1918- January 1919 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - A18-12-OP713: Operative #713 (folder 2 of 2), December 1918- January 1919 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - "Report of Operative #713", December 31, 1918; MS004-211
    - A19-01-OP684: Operative #684, January 1919 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - A19-02-OP798: Operative #798, February-March 1919 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - "Report of Operative #798", February 15, 1919; MS004-212
    - A19-03-OP556: Operative #556 (folder 1 of 6), March-May 1919 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - "Report of Operative #556", March 10, 1919; MS004-213
    - A19-03-OP556: Operative #556 (folder 2 of 6), March-May 1919 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - A19-03-OP556: Operative #556 (folder 3 of 6), March-May 1919 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - A19-03-OP556: Operative #556 (folder 4 of 6), March-May 1919 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - A19-03-OP556: Operative #556 (folder 5 of 6), March-May 1919 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - A19-03-OP556: Operative #556 (folder 6 of 6), March-May 1919 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - A19-06-OP226: Operative #226, June-July 1919 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - "Report of Operative #226", July 13, 1919; MS004-214
    - A19-09-OP136: Operative #136, September 1919 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - A19-09-OP445: Operative #445 (folder 1 of 2), September-November 1919 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - A19-09-OP445: Operative #445 (folder 2 of 2), September-November 1919 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - A19-10-OP18: Operative #18 (folder 1 of 2), October-November 1919 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Report of Operative #18, October 13, 1919; MS004-215
    - A19-10-OP18: Operative #18 (folder 2 of 2), October-November 1919 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Report of Operative #18, November 9, 1919; MS004-216
    - A19-10-OP244: Operative #244, October 1919 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - A19-10-OP259: Operative #259 (folder 1 of 2), October-November 1919 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - A19-10-OP259: Operative #259 (folder 2 of 2), October-November 1919 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Report of Operative #259, November 13, 1919; MS004-217
    - A19-10-OP616: Operative #616 (folder 1 of 2), October 1919 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - A19-10-OP616: Operative #616 (folder 2 of 2), October 1919 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - A19-11-OP249: Operative #249, November 1919 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - A19-12-OP316: Operative #316 (folder 1 of 2), December 1919- February 1920 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Report of Operative #316, January 5, 1920; MS004-218
      - Report of Operative #316, January 23, 1920; MS004-219
      - Report of Operative #316, January 6, 1920; MS004-264
    - A19-12-OP316: Operative #316 (folder 2 of 2), December 1919- February 1920 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Report of Operative #316, February 23, 1920; MS004-220
    - A20-01-OP396: Operative #396 (folder 1 of 2), January-March 1920 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Letter from Harry Preston, Railway Audit and Inspection Company, to Oscar Elsas, January 8, 1920; MS004-221
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to Harry Preston, Railway Audit and Inspection Company, January 16, 1920; MS004-222
    - A19-12-OP316: Operative #396 (folder 2 of 2), January-March 1920 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - A20-02-OP273: Operative #273, February 1920 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - A21-05-OP251: Operative #251 (folder 1 of 10), May-November 1921 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - A21-05-OP251: Operative #251 (folder 2 of 10), May-November 1921 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - A21-05-OP251: Operative #251 (folder 3 of 10), May-November 1921 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - A21-05-OP251: Operative #251 (folder 4 of 10), May-November 1921 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Report of Operative #251, August 7, 1921; MS004-223
      - Report of Operative #251, August 10, 1921; MS004-224
    - A21-05-OP251: Operative #251 (folder 5 of 10), May-November 1921 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Report of Operative #251, August 22, 1921; MS004-226
      - Report of Operative #251, August 29, 1921; MS004-227
    - A21-05-OP251: Operative #251 (folder 6 of 10), May-November 1921 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Report of Operative #251, September 10, 1921; MS004-228
    - A21-05-OP251: Operative #251 (folder 7 of 10), May-November 1921 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - A21-05-OP251: Operative #251 (folder 8 of 10), May-November 1921 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - A21-05-OP251: Operative #251 (folder 9 of 10), May-November 1921 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Report of Operative #251, October 17, 1921; MS004-229
    - A21-05-OP251: Operative #251 (folder 10 of 10), May-November 1921 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - A21-07-OP259: Operative #259, July-August 1921 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Letter from A.J.M. to Oscar Elsas, August 7, 1921; MS004-230
    - A21-09-OP331: Operative #331, August-September 1921 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Letter from the Cue Cluck Rangers to Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills, July 26, 1922; MS004-231
    - A21-09-OP330: Operative #330, September-October 1921 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - A21-11-OP810: Operative #810 (folder 1 of 2), November-December 1921 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - A21-11-OP810: Operative #810 (folder 2 of 2), November-December 1921 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - A22-08-OP330, 331: Operatives #330, 331, August 1922 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Report of Operative #331, August 16, 1922; MS004-232
  - Brooklyn mill, 1919-1920; SERIES 3, Subseries 2; 0.2 Linear feet; (12 folders)
    Subseries 2, Brooklyn, is a small subseries of operative reports for the Brooklyn mill. The reports include information on mill operations, work habits, and union activities.
    - B19-04-OP1042: Operative #1042, April 1919 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - "Report of Operative #1042", April 29, 1919; MS004-233
    - B19-08-OP145: Operative #145 (folder 1 of 2), August-September 1919 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - B19-08-OP145: Operative #145 (folder 2 of 2), August-September 1919 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - "Report of Operative #145", September 6, 1919; MS004-234
    - B19-10-OP747: Operative #747 (folder 1 of 4), October 1919-January 1920 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - "Report of Operative #747", October 29, 1919; MS004-235
    - B19-10-OP747: Operative #747 (folder 2 of 4), October 1919-January 1920 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - "Report of Operative #747", November 18, 1919; MS004-236
    - B19-10-OP747: Operative #747 (folder 3 of 4), October 1919-January 1920 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - "Report of Operative #747", December 12, 1919; MS004-237
      - "Report of Operative #747", December 13, 1919; MS004-238
    - B19-10-OP747: Operative #747 (folder 4 of 4), October 1919-January 1920 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - B20-01-OP80: Operative #80 (folder 1 of 2), January-February 1920 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - B20-01-OP80: Operative #80 (folder 2 of 2), January-February 1920 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - B20-04-OP274: Operative #274 (folder 1 of 3), April-June 1920 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - B20-04-OP274: Operative #274 (folder 2 of 3), April-June 1920 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - B20-04-OP274: Operative #274 (folder 3 of 3), April-June 1920 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Columbus, 1919-1920.; SERIES 3, Subseries 3; 0.5 Linear feet; (2 folders)
    Subseries 3, Columbus, is a small group of operative reports exploring the issues of wages and hours in Columbus mills.
    - C19-03-OP250: Operative #250, March 1919 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - C20-01-OP258: Operative #258, January 1920 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Letter from Harry Preston, Railway Audit and Inspection Company, to Oscar Elsas, January 18, 1920; MS004-239
      - Report of unknown operative, January 7, 1920; MS004-240
  - Dallas mill, 1920.; SERIES 3, Subseries 4; 0.15 Linear feet; (3 folders)
    Subseries 4, Dallas, contains a small number of operative reports concerning mill operations and production at the Dallas mill.
    - D20-03-OP274: Operative #274 (folder 1 of 3), March-May 1920 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - D20-03-OP274: Operative #274 (folder 2 of 3), March-May 1920 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - D20-03-OP274: Operative #274 (folder 3 of 3), March-May 1920 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - New Orleans mill, 1920.; SERIES 3, Subseries 5; 0.1 Linear feet; (4 folders)
    Subseries 5, New Orleans, consists of operative reports concerning production, work habits, and machine repair at the New Orleans location.
    - N20-08-OP274: Operative #274 (folder 1 of 4), August-December 1920 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Letter from Victor Elsas to Oscar Elsas, September 3, 1920; MS004-241
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to Victor Elsas, September 7, 1920; MS004-242
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to Victor Elsas, August 6, 1920; MS004-243
    - N20-08-OP274: Operative #274 (folder 2 of 4), August-December 1920 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - N20-08-OP274: Operative #274 (folder 3 of 4), August-December 1920 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - N20-08-OP274: Operative #274 (folder 4 of 4), August-December 1920 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - St. Louis mill, 1918-1920.; SERIES 3, Subseries 6; 0.3 Linear feet; (15 folders)
    Subseries 6, St. Louis, contains correspondence regarding the quality and placement of operatives, as well as reports on union activities, work habits and attitudes, wages, and mill operations at the St. Louis mill.
    - S18-03-COR: Correspondence, March-May 1918 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - "Some Light on Individual Contract", June 1, 1917; MS004-244
    - S18-04-OP350: Operative #350 (folder 1 of 2), April-June 1918 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - S18-04-OP350: Operative #350 (folder 2 of 2), April-June 1918 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - S18-08-OP360: Operative #360 (folder 1 of 4), August-September 1918 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - S18-08-OP360: Operative #360 (folder 2 of 4), August-September 1918 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - S18-08-OP360: Operative #360 (folder 3 of 4), August-September 1918 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - S18-08-OP360: Operative #360 (folder 4 of 4), August-September 1918 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Report of Operative #360, September 10, 1918; MS004-245
    - S19-04-OP316: Operative #316 (folder 1 of 7), April-June 1919 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - S19-04-OP316: Operative #316 (folder 2 of 7), April-June 1919 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Letter from Charles E. White to Oscar Elsas, May 21, 1919; MS004-247
      - Letter from Oscar Elsas to Charles E. White, May 23, 1919; MS004-248
    - S19-04-OP316: Operative #316 (folder 3 of 7), April-June 1919 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Letter from Charles E. White to Oscar Elsas, May 27, 1919; MS004-249
    - S19-04-OP316: Operative #316 (folder 4 of 7), April-June 1919 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - S19-04-OP316: Operative #316 (folder 5 of 7), April-June 1919 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - S19-04-OP316: Operative #316 (folder 6 of 7), April-June 1919 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Report of Operative #316, May 21, 1919; MS004-246
    - S19-04-OP316: Operative #316 (folder 7 of 7), April-June 1919 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - S20-04-COR: Correspondence, April 1920 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Clippings, 1915-1924.; SERIES 3, Subseries 7; 1.0 folder
    Subseries 7 consists of a single folder of newspaper clippings included in the operative reports.
    - Clippings, 1915-1924 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills - Materials from Emory University, 1872-1994 (bulk 1881-1956).; SERIES 4; 6.0 Linear feet; (eighteen document cases/oversize boxes)
  Provenance
  This series was transferred from MARBL, Emory University, in late 2007. Emory received the donation from Allied Products, the successor to Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills, in about 1985. Emory originally processed this material as MSS614.
  Description
  The fourth series is arranged into three subseries. Subseries 1 contains a variety of materials relating to the history of Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills; Subseries 2 consists of twenty-five ledgers documenting finances and meetings of executive committees and boards of directors; and Subseries 3 is made up of two scrapbooks, which document the history of the company from its earliest years to about 1956.
  - Historical materials on Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills, 1872-1994.; SERIES 4, Subseries 1; 0.4 Linear feet; (one document case)
    Series 4, subseries 1 contains a variety of materials relating to the history of Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills, such as correspondence, by-laws, operational guidelines, and both published and unpublished materials on the company's history.
    Folders are arranged alphabetically by title.
    - Agreement letter, 1895 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - By-laws of Delta Bag Company, ca. 1900 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence; agreement between Jacob Elsas, Isaac May, and Julius Dreyfus, 1954-1958 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Fulton Cotton Spinning Company: By-laws, ca. 1885 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - History: Presidents and board of directors information, ca. 1952 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - History: Published materials, ca. 1929-ca. 1955 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - History: Unpublished materials, 1929-1968 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Materials re: attempts to preserve Fulton Bag and Cotton Mills, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Materials re: textile industry, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Operation guidelines of cotton mill, ca. 1950 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Original check, 1872 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Poster: "reward...", ca. 1914 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Power of attorney form, ca. 1900 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Receiving forms, 1914 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Textile Industries (includes an article on the 100th anniversary of Fulton Bag), December 1968 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Ledgers, 1881-1958.; SERIES 4, Subseries 2; 3.6 Linear feet; (twenty-five ledgers)
    Subseries 2 consists of twenty-five ledgers containing the meeting minutes of the board of directors and executive committees dating from the turn of the twentieth century to the 1950s; private ledgers of financial transactions (including inventories, office pay rolls, balance sheets, financial vouchers, lists of stockholders, and common stocks); and some record books of the branch plants, including the Delta Bag Company of New Orleans (later the New Orleans branch), St. Louis, New York, and Birmingham.
    The ledgers are listed according to type: The minutes ledgers are listed after those that are primarily financial.
    - MS004-L264: Financial ledgers (Common Stocks - includes names of shareholders), 1920-1936 (Box 19)
    - MS004-L265: Financial ledgers (Financial Vouchers - payment vouchers), October 1918-November 1921 (Box 27)
    - MS004-L266: Financial ledgers (Inventory of Fulton Cotton Spinning Company), December 1883-December 1899 (Box 20)
    - MS004-L267: Financial ledgers (Office Pay Rolls - Atlanta and branches), 1910-1918 (Box 20)
    - MS004-L268: Financial ledgers (Private Journal - includes mainly inventory for Atlanta), December 1889-December 1906 (Box 21)
    - MS004-L269: Financial ledgers (Private Journal - includes mainly inventory for Atlanta), December 1907-November 1918 (Box 33)
    - MS004-L270: Financial ledgers (Private Journal - includes a variety of financial information), November 1918-November 1929 (Box 21)
    - MS004-L271: Financial ledgers (Private Ledger - includes a variety of financial information), April 1889-November 1929 (Box 22)
    - MS004-L272: Financial ledgers (Private Ledger - balance sheets, journal vouchers for all branches), November 1929-1951 (Box 23)
    - MS004-L273: Financial ledgers (Private Ledger - profit/loss records), November 1929-November 1952 (Box 22)
    - MS004-L274: Financial ledgers (St. Louis - profit/loss records), 1900-1929 (Box 25)
    - MS004-L288: Minutes, Fulton Cotton Spinning Company (only available on microfilm), February 1881-November 1899 (Box 34)
    - MS004-L275: Minutes, Directors, Atlanta, January 1900-November 1910 (Box 25)
    - MS004-L276: Minutes, Directors, Atlanta, December 1910-March 1913 (Box 25)
    - MS004-L277: Minutes, Directors, Atlanta, April 1913-December 1919 (Box 24)
    - MS004-L278: Minutes, Directors, Atlanta, January 1920-January 1932 (Box 31)
    - MS004-L279: Minutes, Directors, Atlanta, January 1932-November 1943 (Box 24)
    - MS004-L280: Minutes, Directors, Atlanta, January 1943-January 1953 (Box 28)
    - MS004-L281: Minutes, Directors, Delta Bag Company (New Orleans; also available on microfilm), July 1897-February 1911 (Box 29)
    - MS004-L282: Minutes, Directors, New York, May 1901-December 1917 (Box 30)
    - MS004-L283: Minutes, Executive Committee, Atlanta (also includes by-laws), January 1916-July 1922 (Box 31)
    - MS004-L284: Minutes, Executive Committee, Atlanta, July 1922-May 1929 (Box 32)